Don't let it take you off! Hang on! Hang on!
This will work! I can do this!
Kinokami Kagura!
Flame dance!
I still haven't landed a hit.
This won't end until I behead the main body!
It's gone. It must have run off again. But where?
Bastard! Get back here!
You can't run away from your sins!
Demons thrive off killing and devouring humans.
Come on!
Nezuko! Kenya!
Why are you running?
Isn't this just what you've been doing to humans all these years?
Why is every one of you so horribly selfish?
Behold! I call it death throes of the smiths!
Twist the sword and the arch really starts to speak.
Aaaaaaah!
Aaaaaah!
Did you not just try to decapitate a small weak being who's only big enough to fit in the palm of your hand?
God! Your actions are utterly atrocious!
No matter how hard we fight and struggle against them, we humans are powerless.
You're getting in the way. Go hide.
You bastard!
I'm putting an end to this, you stubborn moron!
You mean...
And it seems like you're killing to be a
Again, it breathes off a little too bad.
kiedy thisildaoken
You got it!
Hey, what gives? Why is he so fast?
Damn it! We can't catch up! How does he still have that much strength left in reserve?
We're all going to be reaching our limits soon. If this keeps up, he'll get away.
Daybreak is almost here.
Miss Konroji is giving her all, but it won't be long before she's out of stamina.
And when daybreaks, the demons will escape.
We've got to catch up!
But how? It's so fast!
Damn it! It's planning on just running forever!
Until daybreaks. Until Miss Konroji's worn out.
That's not going to happen!
Because we're not going to let it win!
It's no use! I can't plant my feet!
All because I injured my left leg earlier!
No, it can't end like this! I have to do something!
Tanjiro.
When it comes to thunder breathing, you have to focus on your legs more than anything else.
You see, if you focus on the size of your whole body and the shape of each muscle, it's possible, but it's pretty hard to do.
It's not true total concentration until you're fully aware of each body part.
Well, that's what my grams who trained me used to say, anyway.
Each and every fiber of my muscles, every single vein in my body, circulate air through them.
Channel all your strength into your legs.
Focus!
Explode with a single breath.
And like thunder, slash through the air!
I see you! There's no escape!
Cut through! Cut through! Finish him off!
Use every ounce of strength left!
Don't you fear!
No matter what happens, I have to beheaded!
At least it!
Sorry for someone small like me!
Have you no sympathy?
What gives you the right to bully around the weak?
Answer me!
Drop the victim act!
Yes, if an upper rank could ever be weak!
Don't give me that trap!
Drop the victim act!
stand himself!
No!
I'll...
Hey!
No!
Yo!
I ate demon flesh earlier, so I'm getting burned too!
Tanjiro!
Nesuko!
Damn!
My regeneration is slowing down!
Zohokton's using too much of my power!
I need to replenish myself with human flesh!
I won't let you escape!
Nearby!
I can sense there are humans nearby!
I can sense it!
Get back here!
I'm not letting you escape!
I'll chase you down to the depths of hell!
There's no escape!
I will...
Decapitate you!
AAAAAAHHHHH!
He does threaten an upper rank?
Where are those humans?
If I consume them...
Then I can send that little brat to an early grave in the blink of an eye!
Huh?
Aha!
There's my precious food!
The biggest threat of those three is the demon girl!
She keeps thwarting me at every turn!
Luckily that brat's sword is only able to lodge itself in my neck, not slash it!
First I'll devour those humans!
Then once I've replenished myself!
Crap!
This way!
Right!
It's no use!
You're not getting away!
What do you say?!
What?
Tell me!
What do you try with?
Oh!
That's what she'll do!
Good.
What the fuck?
You're not getting away!
!
That's what she'll call!
Hurry.
You've got to hurry.
One more time.
Use total concentration again.
Tanjiro!
That sword!
Use it!
Tanjiro! Take that sword and go!
Give it back!
Are you out of your mind?
Touch it and I'll kill you!
I only honed it up to the first stage!
It's not done!
Tanjiro! Daybreak's coming!
Don't let him escape!
I ought to kill you!
That hurt!
Tokito!
Thank you!
We're counting on you, Tanjiro!
Mr. Tokito!
Lord Tokito!
Whoa! Mr. Haganesta really did kill him!
What? All I did was hit the kid!
You inhuman!
Calm down, you two!
He passed out from the poison and fever!
Come on!
Take it, Tanjiro.
You inhuman!
Everyone's hopes are in that sword!
Total concentration!
Coming!
Hulka!
Kidukk, Kidukk!
Kidukk, Paammya!
Musined and violently famquillare!
Aangk!
Kidukk!
Dancing Flesh!
I did it. I beheaded the main body.
I did it.
The sun is rising.
There's no protection from the sun here.
Nasuko, run!
Get...
I can't speak.
No.
Nasuko, what are you doing?
It's you.
You're the one in danger.
The sun's coming up.
When the sunlight hits you, you'll die!
Nasuko!
No!
Go find a place in the shade!
Run! Run!
It's not dead!
Even though it's been beheaded!
What?
The word on its tongue is resentment.
But the main body said fear.
Then this one's different.
I messed up.
No matter.
I'll just finish it off!
The sun's not even all the way up yet.
And it's this bad!
Mezuko!
Oh, no!
Somebody!
Kenya!
Tokito!
Who am I kidding?
They can't get you from the top of that cliff in time!
Wait.
That demon should be burning too!
It's no good.
The villagers will be dead before he turns to ash!
And if I run while carrying Mezuko,
I won't make it in time!
What you mean?
Don't move!
Or unable to kill me yet!
Hear me!
Oh!
I don't care!
Fuck!
That demon psychologically belongs to you!
That demon maximizes me!
And I said,
You
too be!
I can't do it.
I can't make up my mind.
Track its scent.
It can't have gotten far.
If the main body broke off and hid far away, the scent would have told me.
It's nearby.
But where?
Pick up its scent.
Its shape.
Its color.
There it is.
It's still inside the demon.
Right then.
Clearer.
Give me a clearer view.
Show me!
I found it.
It's hiding inside the horde.
We're done more!
It caught up!
You're not getting away from me this time!
You coward!
You evil demon!
Atone for your sins!
At the cost of your life!
Why would you do something like stealing from others?
And to make things worse?
You stole from someone kind.
Someone who helped us who can't see.
Out of kindness, our master chose to look the other way.
But I can't forgive you.
I'm going to the magistrate's office.
I'm not the one at fault here.
It's these hands that are to blame.
These hands acted on their own!
What is all of this?
Is that me when I was a human?
Why now after all this time?
I've been told you've committed theft and murder like this
numerous times in another town as well.
I have no sympathy for you.
That's absurd.
I'm not capable of such a thing.
Does someone who's blind?
I know damn well you can see just fine.
I've had a masseur come here to Shirasu before.
However, unlike you, he would face the wall until I started speaking.
You say your hands are to blame?
Then we'll just tie your hands together and sever them!
It'd be a pity if you were beheaded tomorrow, wouldn't it?
What if I told you I could save you?
No matter how you try to fool yourself out of it, the truth remains the same.
Silencing me like this won't do any good.
Is this my life?
A day will come when you have to atone for your sins.
I can only hope that your atonement costs you your life!
Flashing before my eyes.
Plash
Oh, my God.
I won, but I had to sacrifice Nezuko, who was turned to ash by the sun.
Not even her bones from me to bury.
Oh, my God.
Nezuko.
To change Nezuko back into a human, that's the only reason I ever came this far.
Lord Kamado?
Oh, my God.
Hey!
Good...
Good morning.
Next March
Nasuo-Ko!
My Kameno!
Thank goodness.
Are you alright?
You're not hurt.
Thank goodness.
Are you alright?
Right?
No.
Really.
Thank goodness.
You didn't turn to ash and disappear.
I really thought you were dead when you started to burn.
Thank goodness, Nezuko.
I'm so glad you're alright.
Thank goodness.
Oh, yes.
Thank you both for saving us back there.
We never would have forgiven ourselves if Nezuko Paris...
Good for you, Tanjiro.
Nezuko.
You didn't live all of a sudden.
Young Kamado, hang in there, okay?
He died?
He died!
Idiot!
Are you alright?
Stay with us!
Thank goodness.
Nezuko.
I can't take it anymore!
I'm so sorry, but I'm about to be killed!
Yay!
I've been saved!
They must have done it!
They must have beheaded the main body!
Toshikuni?
I'm coming in!
Oh my!
What's gotten into you, Toshikuni, making such a mess like this?
I see you've been doing some research.
Are you having trouble finding a book?
I might be able to help you find it.
But before that, how about taking a break and having some tea with me?
At last!
What's that?
After all these years, someone who's able to withstand the sun has finally appeared.
You've done an excellent job, Han Tengu.
Wow.
You're certainly enjoying it.
Sounds like a very interesting story.
Madam, are you...
Your head...
What happened to it?
If this is true, there's no longer any need to search for the blue spider lily.
Are you okay?
That took so long.
But it was for this reason.
For this reason that for a thousand years,
I've dragged my feet and continue to expand the reach of my kind far beyond my comfort.
A rare constitution that never showed up even among the twelve Kizuki until now.
She's the chosen demon.
If I devour that girl and absorb her properties,
then I too will gain the ability to conquer the accursed sun.
You murdered her!
She's dead!
You killed her!
Master!
Now that I think of it,
it was that day.
It all started one thousand years ago.
Back then, during the period referred to as the Heian era.
If I may, sir.
Your medicine is prepared for you now if you're ready to take it.
What a pathetic shrink.
That said, this inept doctor is the only one I have left to lean on.
What will become of me if I don't take this?
As I'm sure you're well aware,
if you don't take the medicine before you,
you won't live to see your twentieth birthday.
I don't know how effective it will be,
but I'm doing the best I can with what I have.
It's sure to buy you some time, though.
Alright, enough talk.
I'll take it.
It won't work anyway.
How I long to destroy them,
each and every living being.
No matter how many times he examines me,
or administers that damn medicine,
nothing can stop my symptoms from worsening.
Dying is all you're good for,
you incompetent quack.
But soon after,
I began to realize that doctor's medicine had been working.
Unfortunately for him,
it was after I had killed him.
My body was bursting with energy.
My feeble physique was replaced with a much more formidable one.
But there was one problem.
My body forbade me from stepping into the sunlight.
There was no doubt in my mind.
If I were to be exposed to it,
I would die.
I quickly began to crave human flesh and blood.
To satisfy my hunger,
I devoured countless humans.
And if anyone were to stand in the way of doing that,
I'd simply eliminate them.
That's all there is to it.
Face me!
You cursed demon who disrupts our peace!
Are you...
talking to me right now?
I had gained power beyond my imagination.
Eternal power.
But having to restrict my movements during the day
was nothing short of humiliating.
My anger was reaching its boiling point.
It was then
that I began to seek a body
that wouldn't perish in the sunlight.
I examined the compounds from the doctor's elixir.
But because it was still experimental,
I couldn't decipher how to make the medicine
referred to as
Blue Spider Lily.
Based on my research,
it appeared to contain actual blue-colored spider lilies.
But as for where this blue spider lily bloomed,
or if it was even possible to cultivate anymore,
no one knew but the doctor I had killed.
I searched every corner of Japan,
but failed to find anything.
In order to become truly immortal,
finding the blue spider lily,
or another of my kind
who somehow possessed the ability to survive the sunlight,
have been my top priorities to this moment.
And at long last,
I have found her.
Now that I've located a demon who has conquered the sun,
there's no longer any reason to extend my reach.
I will absorb her,
for it is my destiny to conquer the loathsome sunlight.
Once I get my hands on Nezuko,
I'll become a perfect being,
immune to the diseases of change and death!
Tanjiro, are you alright?
Tanjiro, I can't thank you enough.
If you say so.
But more importantly,
what's going on with Nezuko?
Uh, well, actually...
Why you...
What did you do with my unfinished sword?
Please calm down!
Mr. Hageneska?
I asked you what happened to the sword I was honing,
you ungrateful little brat!
Oh, right!
I fought an upper rank with it!
So you used it to fight, huh?
To fight and...
Huh?
Then what happened?
I blacked out and then...
Oh, you mean this sword?
Did you break it?
Uh, no!
If you broke it,
you better fash up!
I didn't break it!
No, wait!
It's here!
I am going to kill you!
Nezuko, run for it!
Get back here!
Mr. Hageneska!
Hold down!
Look!
The sword is right over here!
I can't face my fury!
Come on!
You guys!
Ha ha ha!
Oh my god!
You guys!
Ha ha ha ha!
Miss Konroji!
Ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
We did it!
I can't believe we pulled that off!
It's a miracle that we're all still alive!
Thank goodness!
Ha ha ha ha!
Huh?
Oh yes, thank goodness!
Ha ha ha!
Whaaaaat?
Uh, hey Tanjiro!
What is it?
I'm so glad you're safe!
She's talking again, but her eyes and fangs are the same.
I don't understand it, and yet, I'm so relieved she's alive.
That I don't think I really need to.
Thank goodness you're safe!
Thank goodness!
Ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Thank goodness!
Mr. Tanjiro, I thank you for providing me with the blood from Ms. Nezuko and the Twelve Kizuki,
and for helping me with all my research up until now.
The man in Asakusa who was turned into a demon by Muzan has regained his sense of self.
And it's all thanks to Ms. Nezuko's blood.
Released from Muzan's control, he can now live normally off a small amount of blood.
The transformation of Ms. Nezuko's blood is surprising.
The components of her blood have mutated again and again in such a short amount of time.
And so, lately, I can't help but think, why is it Ms. Nezuko has yet to regain her sense of self and remain stuck in a childlike state?
I believe that deep down in her mind, there's something more important than regaining her sense of self.
Something that she needs to prioritize above it.
Yushiro? Yushiro?
Yes? Lady Tamayo? What can I do for you?
Can you fetch Chachamaru?
As you requested, Chachamaru's ready to go.
Give my regards to the Kamado siblings. Safe travels.
Mr. Tanjiro, please know, this is pure speculation on my part.
But I believe that it won't be long...
Before Ms. Nezuko is able to conquer the Sun.
Make way! Coming through!
Out there!
Come on, look us up!
This'll work just right.
Why don't you...
That's right.
Get out of the way!
Over here!
He's out there!
That's right!
Bring that!
Yes!
That should look...
Hey! Lord Techin!
Ah! Kotetsu!
Mr. Tanjiro's leaving the village, so he'd like to say goodbye.
Mr. Tanjiro?
Feeling any better after resting?
Yes.
Thank you for all that you did for me.
I'm also grateful that you provided me with this card as well.
Please, I should be the one who's thanking you.
You did a stupendous job protecting this village. I'm in your debt.
I wasn't able to do that much all on my own. The others helped more. Our combined strength, and that sword which connects us to ancient hope. That is the reason we were able to beat those upper rank demons.
Yes, yes. You're quite right. And where's your little sister?
She's asleep. Her body's gotta be exhausted.
I see. Well, I'm truly glad to hear she's alright.
Yes.
Eh?
Kanamori, is it me, or is that Hotaru lurking around over there?
It's him.
What is he doing?
I guess he's still upset, so he's trying to hide. He won't forgive Mr. Tanjiro for using a sword before it was fully honed.
What am I going to do with that guy?
Hotaru! Come over here a second!
Quit dilly-dallying and come over here!
Hotaru!
I'm telling you, it's all his fault!
Right? Am I right? Am I right?
Sorry, but that really hurts!
Hotaru!
But wait! If Mr. Tanjiro and the others hadn't come to help, the village would have been destroyed!
Now, Hotaru, the real reason you came here was to greet Tanjiro, wasn't it? He came all the way here to speak to you.
Hmm.
Mr. Haganesca, thank you for always taking care of my sword. I appreciate it. The reason that I came here was to thank you for doing that.
I... I'll begin honing your sword for you right away. Standby at the Butterfly Mansion.
You're going to repair it for me?
Of course I am! Don't you want it fixed?
Thank you very much!
Sure!
Mr. Haganesca, don't tell me you're embarrassed!
Kotatsu, stop!
Careful, young Kotatsu!
That's pretty funny, huh?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
No way am I embarrassed!
Seems young Kotatsu dug himself an early grave.
But really, thank you for everything you've done. Now, I have to get back to training again!
Yes. Best of luck to you. Safe travels, Kakushi! I'm counting on you to get him there.
Huh?
Right. Just as you did coming here. You'll have to put these on again.
Uh-oh!
Alright! Take care, everybody!
I wish you good health!
Be careful out there!
Please come back soon, okay?
Bye, everyone!
Um, why are we stopping here?
Mr. Tanjiro.
Tanjiro!
Take some space!
Thank you!
Take care!
You can count on us, but take care of yourself!
Please!
Thank you, Tanjiro!
Thank you!
You're a hero!
Yeah!
aiah perchéしら...
Shall we do without the blindfold and nose plugs
until we've crossed the perimeter of the village?
Yes!
Thanks!
See you!
Thanks again!
Thank you!
Take care!
Thank you.